const questions = [
    { category: 'A1', question: "Soal Matematika 1", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], correct: 2 },
    { category: 'A1', question: "Soal Matematika 2", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], correct: 3 },
    { category: 'B1', question: "Soal Fisika 1", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], correct: 0 },
    { category: 'B1', question: "Soal Fisika 2", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], correct: 1 },
    { category: 'C1', question: "Soal Biologi 1", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], values: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5] },
    { category: 'C1', question: "Soal Biologi 2", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], values: [5, 4, 3, 2, 1] }, 
    { category: 'A1', question: "Soal Matematika 1", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], correct: 2 },
    { category: 'A1', question: "Soal Matematika 2", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], correct: 3 },
    { category: 'B1', question: "Soal Fisika 1", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], correct: 0 },
    { category: 'B1', question: "Soal Fisika 2", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], correct: 1 },
    { category: 'C1', question: "Soal Biologi 1", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], values: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5] },
    { category: 'C1', question: "Soal Biologi 2", options: ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E"], values: [5, 4, 3, 2, 1] }
];
